北边  西边  南边  汇报
North, West, South, report.
你那话是什么意思
What does that mean?
就是我说的意思
What I said.
你希望他能活下去
You hope the guy makes it.
这不够
That's not enough.
-如果你他妈在乎...  -卡尔
- If you give a shit -- ‭- Carl.
如果你在乎  就做点什么
If you care, you do something.
不要只是希望
You don't just hope.
仅仅希望是不够的
It takes more than that.
我就这意思
That's what I meant.
战斗过后会有收获
There's gonna be something after the fight's over.
不是每个人都有
Not for everyone.
好吧  但是
Okay, yeah, but...
你的收获是什么
What about for you?
跟照片上不同
Different from picture.
简迪斯
Jadis!
子弹来自窗户
It's coming from the window!
我们反击  然后撤退
We hit it and fall... back.
快走
Go!
他们逃出来了
They got out.
没过多久  我们得警告大家
It hasn't been long. We have to warn everyone.
他们会反击的
They're gonna hit back.
我们可以在东边哨点附近弄到车  然后分头走
We can get the cars near the East lookout and split up.
也许得找别的车
Might have to find other rides.
狙击手可能开车逃走了
The snipers probably used theirs to get away.
我想他们没逃走
I don't think they got away.
你会活下去的  爸爸
You're gonna live, Dad.
我们为什么要这样做
Why are we doing this?
为什么要反抗他们
Why are we fighting them?
不就是为了不让他们如愿吗
So it isn't like how they want it,
不让大家为他们工作
with everyone working for them,
不让大家为他们活着
everyone living for them?
我们反抗是为了所有人一起奋斗
We're fighting so it's all of us working together
不仅仅是为了杀别人
for something more than just killing other people.
你觉得我们以后
Well, you think ‭we're gonna be out there,
会跟尼根一起摘草莓吗
picking strawberries with Negan?
如果有必要的话
If that's what it takes.
仅仅希望是不够的
It's more than just hope.
难道我们要杀光他们所有人吗
What, are we just gonna kill all of them?
找到前进的办法更难
Finding some way forward, that's harder.
更有意义
That's something more.
爸爸  必须那样
Dad, ‭that's how it's got to be.
《行尸走肉》
他们一定会跟我们谈  对吧
They have to talk to us, right?
毕竟我们远道而来
After coming all this way?
抱歉
Sorry.
我只是
I was just...
怎么了
What?
埃里克和我之前会像这样
Eric and I used to take trips like this...
开车寻找幸存者
back when we were looking for people
带回亚历山大
to bring to Alexandria.
我们几天前开去了山顶寨
We drove to the Hilltop just a few days ago
帮忙为车上装甲
and...helped armor those cars.
他就在你现在坐的地方
He was always right there, where you are now.
我只是
I was just...
想起了那一切
remembering that.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我得确保他的死有意义
I need to make sure he died for a reason.
你刚在说什么
Tell me what you were saying?
我在说
I was, uh...
我在想海边旅馆
I was just thinking about Oceanside.
想知道她们会不会跟我们谈
Wondering if they'll talk to us.
希望她们会
I hope so.
我们尽量别惊动她们
We got to try not to scare them.
塔拉说过  在遇见她之前
Tara said that, up until her,
她们都是见人就杀的
they killed on sight.
这次风险很大
It's going to be a risk.
我们需要她们的支持
We need to have them be a part of this.
我们需要说服她们
We just have to convince them.
必须说服
We have to.
我们应该把枪带来还给她们
We should've brought guns for them.
我们必须留着那些枪
We have to hold on to those guns.
我可以把我的枪给辛蒂
I could give Cyndie mine.
你必须得有枪  伊妮德
You're gonna need your gun, Enid.
是啊
Right.
真希望这一切在我用到枪之前就结束了
I just want it to end before that.
我也希望
I do, too.
你会开车吗
You know how to drive?
会
Uh, yeah.
算会吧
Well, sort of.
反正比卡尔开得好
I'm better than Carl, anyways.
你为什么转向了
Why are you turning?
我们应该径直朝前的
We're supposed to be going straight.
我想去看一个东西
Uh, I just want to check something out.
就是想给她们准备一些她们用得上的东西
Maybe it's just about giving them something they can use.
说得对
You're right.
我们不能空手去
We can't show up empty-handed.
社交礼仪
Social graces. ‭
罗阿诺克酿酒厂
前方2英里
我们很快就回来
We'll be back soon.
我会把你爸爸也带回来  好吗
I'll bring your daddy, too, okay?
能和我说"拜拜"吗
Can you say bye-bye?
-拜拜  -拜
- Bye-bye. -‭Bye.
很高兴你回来了
I'm glad you came back.
我们一起行动比较好
It's better we go out there together.
计划成功了
It worked.
我们冲进去  让他们投降
We'll roll in, tell them to give up.
他们就会投降了
They're gonna give up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我没做到
I couldn't.
不用道歉
Don't be.
成功了
It worked.
爸爸
无论如何都要活下去
成功了
It worked.
我们撞开了门  行尸进去了
We opened it up for the walkers. They're in.
好
Okay.
那我们一鼓作气做完  按计划来
So we'll finish it, just like we planned.
好
Yeah.
你回来时去了那间仓库吗
You stop by that warehouse on your way back?
有找到什么枪支弹药吗
Find any guns, ammo?
没  没什么重武器
No, nothing heavy.
只有一些闪光弹  烟雾弹...
Just some stun grenades, smoke grenades...
还有汽笛  八成是用来引行尸的
air horn, probably for redirects.
好吧
Cool.
他们投降之后
Well, after they surrender,
我们可以用这些东西引开尸群
we should use this stuff to redirect the herd.
我们该带上这些东西
We should take it with us.
好  没问题
Yeah. That's good.
堆起来
Yeah, stack it up.
没错  继续放
Yeah, keep going.
太好了
Great.
那个看起来很重的箱子呢
What about that really heavy-looking crate?
棒极了
Awesome.
汽笛呢
What about the air horn?
酷  好吧
Cool. Okay.
没问题
Sure.
好  我能行
Yeah, I got it.
罗阿诺克酿酒厂
这里可以吗
This good?
不知道
I don't know.
是个不错的地方
It's as good a place as any.
是啊
Yeah.
你不该来这里
You shouldn't have come here.
放下枪  马上
Drop it! Now!
站起来  慢点
Get up. Slow.
祖母
Grandma?
Grandma!
天啊
Oh, God!
不要
No!
卡尔
Carl.
我一直在找你
I've been lookin' for you.
我们准备出发了
We're about ready to head out.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在帮某人
I'm helping someone.
一个旅人
A traveler.
在下水道里
In the sewer?
你们可能想知道
You may be wondering
为什么你们的哨兵没拉响警报
why the hell your lookouts didn't sound the alarm.
看  我们很客气
See, we are polite.
我也不知他们何时能从枪伤中醒来
I mean, I don't know when they're gonna wake up from that kinda shot,
但他们应该会"醒来"的
but they should wake up.
所以就别拐弯抹角了
So let's just cut through the cow shit...
你们输了
you lose.
都结束了
It's over.
在你们的小房子前面排好队
So you're gonna line up in front of your little houses,
好好想想该怎么道歉
and you're gonna work up some apologies,
表现最差的那个人
and then the person with the lamest one
会被杀
is gonna get killed.
接着我会当着大家的面杀了瑞克  作为了结
Then I kill Rick in front of everybody, and we move on.
你们有三分钟时间打开大门
You have three...count 'em, three minutes to open this gate,
否则我们就把你们轰个稀巴烂
or we start bombing the shit out of you!
他们逃出来了
They got out.
快
Come on.
米琼恩
Michonne.
快走
Come on!
陛下
我不得不走了
我们说过要去  不能说话不算话
我希望胜利时我能在场
我希望你也在场  兄弟
杰瑞
你觉得他们会投降吗
Do you think they'll surrender?
会的
They will.
终归会的
Eventually.
现在不会吗
Not now?
我们会那么快就放弃吗
Would we give up that quick?
不会
No, we wouldn't.
那当然
Damn straight.
他们今天不投降  很快也会投降的
They don't surrender today, they will soon.
只要断粮  断水
Just need to run out of food...water...
没了选择
choices.
慢点
Slow down.
怎么回事
What is it?
以前路中间没有树
Tree in the road wasn't there before.
可能是自己倒下来的
Could've fallen on its own.
树有时会这样
Trees do that.
是他们
It's them.
出事了
Something happened.
伯蒂  调头
Bertie, turn around.
伯蒂
Bertie!
玛姬
Maggie.
该死
Oh, shit.
你们好呀
Hello, hello, hello!
今晚夜色真美
What a damn nice night.
你得假装我们要从后面逃跑
You need to make it look like we're escaping out back.
进丛林  在去采石场的半途中
Get to the woods, halfway to the quarry,
把灯熄灭
and cut the lights.
和他们拉开距离
Get enough of a lead on them,
攻击他们  然后徒步逃走
hit them, and get away on foot.
你知道我们会在哪
You know where we'll be.
只要拿上枪  把其他人带过来
Just have to get the guns, get everyone else here,
我们会在那汇合
and we'll meet you there.
剩两分钟了  各位
Two minutes, people!
加把劲
Dig deep.
我要永生难忘的道歉
I want these apologies to be memorable.
创意还能加分
Bonus points for creativity.
写首诗  唱首歌
Work up a poem, sing a song.
我他妈最爱了
I love that shit.
去吧
Get going.
医务室里有人
There's gonna people in the infirmary.
他们需要你们的帮助
They're gonna need your help.
我们有枪
Look, we got guns.
我们能对抗他们
We can fight them.
我们可以  但不是现在
We will, but not now.
卡尔说得对
Carl's right.
卡尔  这地方不能拱手让人
Carl, we can't just let them have this place.
能的
We can.
你的任务是活过今晚
All you need to do is survive tonight.
这次由我做主  你说过的
This is my show. You said it.
这是我的计划  你得照做
This is my plan, and you're gonna do it.
你们都得照做
You're all gonna do it.
出发吧
So let's go!
还剩一分钟
One minute!
大家都来了
Well, here we are.
我也不想闹成这样
I didn't want it to come to this.
我今晚宁愿待在家里
Much rather would've been at home tonight.
但你们想点菜单上没有的菜
But you folks wanted to order off the menu.
瞧瞧
And look at that!
现在你们得吃屎了
Now you have to eat shit.
我也不想喂你们吃屎
God knows I didn't want to be the one serving it up.
神之国和其子民  此刻起由尼根接管
The Kingdom and everyone in it now belongs to Negan.
从今往后
Moving forward,
你们所生产的一切都归我们
everything that you produce will belong to us.
我们会留给你们
We're going to give you
足以支撑你们干活的分量
just enough to keep you working,
不过你们应该很快就会减掉那圈婴儿肥
but you're probably going to lose the freshman 15 pretty quick.
此外
In addition,
所有身体健全的男女
all able-bodied men and women
都将被送往救世堂
will also be transported to the Sanctuary
负责修补和重建
to see to its repair and refurbishment.
还有
And...
因为你们把我们的家
since you made our former home
弄得到处是死人和行尸
a goddamn mess of death and the dead,
我们只好先住这了
we'll be hanging our hat here.
你们都懂会发生什么
You all know the drill.
你们近来的决定改变了一切
Due to your recent decisions, everything has changed.
但一切又没有改变
And yet, nothin' has changed.
所有人必须上交枪支
Everyone needs to hand over their guns.
加里  有人轻举妄动就毙了那混蛋
Gary, shoot that beautiful bastard if anyone tries anything.
车里的人也一样
Same goes for everyone in the cars.
好吧
Okeydokey.
这是你自找的  瑞克
Brought this on yourself, Rick.
我想和你们合作
See, I was willing to work with you.
你们只要遵守一些很简单的规则
All you had to do was follow a few very simple rules.
现在
Now --
现在你们只能去死了
Well, now I see that you got to go.
徒留焦土吧  混蛋们
Scorched earth, you dick!
他不在家
He's not home.
我勒个去
Oh-ho-holy shit!
所有人都别开火  是卡尔
Everybody hold your fire. It's Carl.
看看你
Look at you.
像个大孩子一样来应门
Answering the door like a big boy.
我真是自豪
I am so proud.
爸爸不在家吗
Daddy's not home, huh?
我想他回来后将看到惊喜烟花秀的
Well, I guess he's gonna get back to a big old smoky surprise.
这里有很多家庭
There's families in here.
孩子们
Kids.
我妹妹
My little sister.
真让老子心碎
Well, that shit just breaks my heart.
救世堂也有孩子们
There's kids at the Sanctuary.
你肯定看到过他们
You must've seen 'em.
某个哨站里甚至有个小宝宝
Even had a little baby at one of the outposts.
不知道她怎么样了
I wonder what happened to her.
没什么是公平的  孩子
None of this shit's fair, kid.
你很清楚
Hell, you know that.
你不得不亲手杀了你妈妈
You had to kill your own mom.
真是太残忍了
That is screwed up.
因此  我们需要有人出来做主
Ergo, ‭we need someone in charge
愿意不惜一切代价
who's willing to do whatever it takes
确保不会再发生那种事
to make sure that shit doesn't happen.
等等
Oh. Wait.
那个人就是我
That's me.
坏事确实会发生
Bad stuff does happen,
但我们可以想办法
but we can figure this out.
我们能阻止这一切
We can stop this.
现在你又想谈了
Oh, now you want to talk?
你爸爸说不管怎样我都得死
See, your dad had it that I died, no matter what.
他给了我的手下选择
He gave my people a choice.
没给我
Not me.
现在我们要达成新的共识
Now we're gonna need a new understanding.
-道歉  惩罚  -杀了我
- Apologies, punish-- - Kill me.
你说什么
What did you say?
如果你必须杀人
If you have to kill someone,
必须惩罚  那就杀了我
if there has to be punishment, then kill me.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
你想死吗
You wanna die?
我不想
No, I don't.
但我会死
But I will.
总会死的
It's gonna happen.
如果我的死能阻止这一切
And I-- if me dying could stop this,
如果能做出一些改变...
if it can make things different --
对我们  对你
for us, for you, ‭
对其他的那些孩子们  那就值了
for all those other kids -- it'd be worth it.
难道原本计划是这样吗
I mean, was this the plan?
难道应该是这样吗
Was it supposed to be this way?
你原本想变成这样的人吗
Is this who you wanted to be?
汽车挡不住的  小德
Cars aren't gonna be enough, D.
我们应该用卡车
We should've had the trucks.
不  能挡住
No, it'll hold.
准备好清理吧
Just get ready for cleanup.
真该死
Well, I'll be damned.
快点  追上他们
Come on! Let's get 'em!
有车队逃出  我们在追
Got a convoy out. We're on 'em.
狗娘养的  卡尔
Son of a bitch, Carl!
刚那只是演戏吗
Was that just a play?!
我还以为咱俩动真感情了
I thought we were havin' a moment,
小王八羔子
you little asshole!
全炸了
Bombs away!
现在  最后一件事
Now, there's one last piece of business.
这地方有一个人
There's ....one person here
得对发生的这一切负责
who has to answer for all of this.
以西结
Ezekiel.
我要他
I need him.
我们还没找到他
We haven't found him yet.
我不指望有谁会把他交出来
I don't expect anyone to give him up.
但我想说
But I will say,
帮自己一个忙  合作一点
to do yourselves a favor and cooperate now.
我们在那片废墟里
We didn't see any goons with dreadlocks
没看见那个扎着脏辫的白痴
back at what was left of the homestead,
所以他肯定在这
so he's gotta be here.
我们有规矩  而他坏了规矩
There are rules, and he broke them!
你要是再不交出他
And if you do not give him up right now,
一场惨剧就将上演
this...moves into something traumatic.
我不想这样
I don't want that.
别再火上浇油了
Don't make this any worse than it already is.
还有孩子在场呢
There's goddamn kids here.
他们不需要看到这些
They don't need to see this shit.
那好
All right.
你们还有五分钟
You got five minutes.
然后就按尼根的方式来
Then it's Negan's way.
这都怪你们
And that's on you.
不怪我
Not me.
你们怎么逃出来的
How'd you get out?
让你猜三次
Three guesses.
就当我们想到了办法吧
Well, let's just say we figured it out.
-你对其他人干了什么  -没错
- What'd you do to the others - ‭Oh, yes!
我正要说这事呢
That's exactly where I was going next.
现在神之国正在众目睽睽之下
Right now, Kingdom is getting its innards splayed out
被开膛破肚
for the world to see.
从今晚开始  救世军会接管那里
And the Saviors will be taking possession of that property, starting tonight.
亚历山大也一样
Same with Alexandria.
只要他们不把事情复杂化
As long as they don't make it complicated.
但是山顶寨呢
But Hilltop?
那些农民
The farmers?
我们新社会的产粮区
The breadbasket ‭of our nascent civilization?
今天你们走运了
It's your lucky day.
你们将继续生产粮食
You've been chosen to keep producing.
格雷戈里让我在老大面前出了点洋相
Gregory made a little bit of a fool out of me in front of the big man,
所以我希望你能够弥补过错
so I am hoping that you are the one to make things right.
听到了吗
You hear that?
我要你好好听着
I need you to shift into active listening.
尤金
Eugene!
顺便一提
Who, by the way,
之前我对他深表怀疑
I was admittedly skeptical of,
但老天  干得漂亮
but, man, worked out like gangbusters.
他帮我们逃出了
He helped us get out of the situation
冷血行尸大军的包围
with the masses of the cold and impolite.
我的手下正在引开剩下的尸群
And now my guys are leading the rest of the herd away.
所以
So...
这事只会有两种结果
this can go one of two ways.
第一  我可以杀了跪在那边的好好先生
One, ‭I can kill this likable gent on his knees over there,
把你从车上拖下来
drag you out of this car,
装进这个棺材里
and put you in this box.
你不会在里面窒息而亡
In which you will not suffocate to death...
像你的朋友
like your friend.
萨沙一样
Sasha.
然后我们带你到山顶寨
And then we take you to Hilltop,
把所有人聚起来
gather everyone up,
在他们面前杀了你
and kill you ‭in front of the whole place.
之后再把你运回救世堂
And then drag you back to Sanctuary
插在总部前面的矛上
and put on the spike in front of HQ.
接着  我的人会把尸群引到山顶寨
And then my people ‭will lead the walker herd
把你们没能成功剿灭我们的招数
to the Hilltop and pull off the same move
用在你们身上
that your people tried unsuccessfully at our place.
这对所牵涉到的人都是一大烦心事啊
What a pain in the ass for everyone concerned.
或者第二  你掉头  回家
Or two, you turn around, go home,
开始灌溉高粱
start watering that sorghum,
为每个人  最重要的是  为我
save everyone, ‭and, most importantly, me,
省下许多麻烦
a lot of trouble.
而且  没错
And, yeah...
到时我们得杀死你们其中一人
we're gonna have to kill one of your people.
但之后我们就是好伙伴了
But then we're aces.
不  加里
Nah, Gary.
我来
I got this.
我非常需要你明白
I just really needed you
我在说什么
to know what I was talkin' about.
我需要你闻到血味
I need you to smell it.
现在告诉我  我不必杀掉
Now tell me I don't got to kill
这位长发飘飘的先生
this gent with the lustrous mane.
告诉我  我不必继续杀人
Tell me I don't got to go down the line!
告诉我  玛姬
Tell me, Maggie!
-加里  -不
- Gary! - ‭No!
你什么都不用做
You don't need to do any of it.
我只想请你帮个忙
I just want to ask you a favor.
什么忙
What is that?
我想要那个棺材
I'd like that box.
把尼尔装在里面  带回家葬了
Take Neil home, to bury him in.
我答应你
Favor granted.
他们逃出来
They didn't get out
不是因为我们用卡车撞了个豁口
because of what we did with the truck.
就算是  也只是个错误
Even if they did, it was just a mistake.
我也犯过一个错
And I made one, too.
如果我没去救世堂杀尼根
If I hadn't gone to the Sanctuary to kill Negan,
也许萨沙还活着
maybe Sasha would still be alive.
也许她自己就去了
Maybe she would've gone herself.
也许所有事最后
Maybe everything would've ended up going
还是同样的结果
exactly the same way.
我不希望你们这么做
I didn't want you guys to do it,
但也许这是你们需要的
but maybe you needed to.
也许你们需要执行到底
Maybe you needed to play things out
才能想明白
to figure shit out.
他们到底在哪
Where the hell are they?
停车
Stop the car.
我就想走近一点看
I just want to take a closer look.
小德  快停车
D, stop the damn car!
你要把卡车引过去了
You're leading the trucks right into it!
你会害死我们的
You're gonna get us killed!
就现在
Now!
这就是你不用卡车堵门的原因
That's why you didn't want to block the gate with the trucks.
这就是你开过来的原因
That's why you drove right up to this!
叛徒是你
It was you!
都是你做的
All of it!
你快叫他们住手
You tell them to stop!
不管用的
It doesn't work like that.
见鬼
Well, shit.
我们可以用上那些东西的
We coulda used those.
太阳能板
Solar panels?
车队跑掉了是吧
That convoy, they got away, huh?
全跑掉了吗
All of 'em?
那个小孩应该还在这
Kid's still gotta be here.
我觉得他想破釜沉舟
I think he wanted to go down with the ship.
搜查这里
Search the place.
找到他  把他捆起来
Find him, tie him up.
别杀他
Don't kill him.
炸掉剩下所有房子
Blow up every other house.
我要去瑞克家里做个意面
I'm gonna go to Rick's, make a little spaghetti.
如果他来了  送来见我
When he shows up, send him my way.
趴在地上  孩子
On the ground, kid!
该死  走吧
Dammit. Come on!
我勉强同意帮助你实现愿望
I will acquiesce and facilitate your wishes,
尽管这是有勇无谋的行为
regardless of the foolhardiness.
但是  就我个人而言  我真诚地认为
However, on a personal note, it is my sincere opinion
从这间小医务室里冒险出逃
that venturing from the confines of this infirmary
将会是一个致命的错误
will be a fatal mistake.
医生有足够的能力自行归寨
The doctor is more than capable of returning on his own.
而你很可能在途中死于疾病
You, on the other hand, will likely succumb to illness
或被撕碎
or bodily rending en route.
但我知道这是你选择的攻略
But I know that that's the stratagem you're choosing,
而这是个肮脏的游戏
and it's a dirty game.
你们谁能告诉我
Will one of you please tell me
到底是怎么回事
what the hell is going on?
加百利认为他肩负着一项上帝的使命
Gabriel believes he's on a mission from God
要送你回到山顶寨
to return you to Hilltop
为玛姬和格伦的孩子接生
to tend to the birthing of Maggie and Glenn's child.
他哪里都去不了
Look, he -- he can't go anywhere.
那是你们俩接下来需要单独讨论的事
That is a conversation the two of you need to have sotto, solo.
我只是来告诉你
I'm just here to inform you
北区大门的守卫已经崩坏了
that the guard at the Northside gate is OOC.
在此情报下  你选择做与不做
What you choose to do or not do with that knowledge
-都与我无关  -等等
- is none of my beeswax or card stacks. - Wait.
你杀了一个守卫吗
You killed a guard?
没有
No.
他的咖啡被换掉了
His coffee was compromised.
他现在正坐着瓷质巴士
He's currently riding a porcelain bus
享受泻药和融化的无糖口香糖带来的腹泻
with laxative and melted sugar-free-gum-induced diarrhea.
事实上  除非他健步如飞
In fact, unless he was fleet of foot,
他现在非常有可能
he may very well be
已经灾难性地拉在了他的卡其裤里
catastrophically crapping his khakis right now.
为什么要这么做
Why?
只是
Just, uh...
今晚想睡个好觉
....plan on sleeping tonight.
那跟我们一起走吧
So come with us.
还不算太晚
It's not too late.
他们会原谅你的
They'll take you back.
我不应该那样做
I shan't be doin' that.
糟糕
Oops.
我好像刚掉了把车钥匙
I seem to have dropped the keys to a vehicle
车就停在刚才说过的北区大门外
located just outside the aforementioned Northside gate.
你在做正确的事情
You're doing the right thing.
正如之前的争论  正确与否是相对的
As previously debated, that assessment is relative.
不
No.
不是的
It isn't.
你们看我干什么
What're you lookin' at me for?!
去啊
Go!
那是以西结  我们得活捉他
That's Ezekiel! We need him alive.
那该死的国王比其他人都值钱
Goddamn King's worth more than all of 'em.
快去
Go!
娜比拉  以西结在哪
Nabila! Where's Ezekiel?
他还在里面  应该吧
He's still in there -- I think.
我也不知道
I don't know.
你得领大家去安全的地方
You've got to get everyone to safety.
走库克曼大道去金斯利
Take Cookman Parkway to Kingsley,
米色房子  两英里外
beige house, 2 miles down.
有个栅栏  我在那里和你汇合
It's got a fence. I'll meet you there.
陛下
Your Majesty.
救救他们
Save 'em...
就像你当初救我一样
like you saved me.
等等
Wait.
以西结  不要
Ezekiel, no!
玛格丽特  我明白你为何把我关在这里
Margaret, I -- I understand you putting me in here,
我懂你的意思  但是...
a-a-and message received, but...
-你知道我不属于这里  -闭嘴
- you know I don't belong in here. - Shut up.
在外面发生了什么
What happened out there?
那家伙
That one.
放出来
Get him out.
他能出去吗
He gets out?
玛姬  你要干什么
Maggie, what are you doing?
凯尔  把枪给我
Kal, I need your gun.
这家伙之前想杀你
This one tried to kill you.
玛姬  你不想这样做的
Maggie, you don't wanna do this.
闭嘴  凯尔
Shut up, Al!
小甜心想作秀  就让她作吧
If Cupcake wants to put on a show, let her put on a show.
你想当下一个吗
You wanna be next?
不想
No, I don't.
救世军今天在路上杀了我们的人
Saviors killed one of our own tonight on the road.
这事还没扯平  但这是个开始
We aren't even, but that was a start.
玛姬
Maggie.
加派警卫看守周围
Get more guards on duty.
加固防护墙  把尼尔埋了
Start fortifying the walls and bury Neil.
天一亮  其他人都去打理庄稼
First light, everybody else starts tending crops.
我们不是不放弃吗
I thought we don't give up.
没错  我们不放弃
No, we don't.
西蒙说其他人也被袭击了
Simon said the others are under attack,
也就是说没有新的补给品来了
which means there's no more supplies going in,
但可能会有人来
but there might be people.
我们得做好准备
We have to be ready.
山顶寨必须当最后的堡垒
Gonna be up to Hilltop to make the last stand.
结束了
It's over!
我确保了你们能从后面逃出去
I made sure you guys could get out the back.
我把车直接开到了路障前
I drove the convoy ‭right up to the roadblock.
我知道那是什么
I knew what it was.
我不能回去了
I can't go back.
有个人跑了
One of 'em got away.
她会告诉他们的
She's gonna tell them.
他们是怎么逃出去的
How'd they get out?
是因为我做的事吗
Was it what I did?
是因为尤金
Eugene.
我还能帮你们
I can still help you.
我了解他们的行事规则  知道尼根的思维方式
I know how they work, how Negan thinks.
我希望你们赢
I want you to win.
我想让尼根死
I want Negan to die.
其余的事之后再了结
And we can settle up after.
我们得回去  立刻回去
We need to get back -- now.
我们人质多38个  别轻举妄动
放在他们能看见的地方
Leave it where they'll find it.
我们本来合作愉快
‭We had a good thing going.
对那孩子的事我也很难过
I felt bad about the kid, too.
我不希望那样  你知道的
I didn't want that. You know that!
现在要死很多很多人
And now a lot more people have to die.
有时候你必须忍气吞声
Sometimes you just have to swallow it!
我就是这样
I do.
天啊  我以为你也懂的
Jesus, I thought you knew that, too.
我喜欢你  以西结
I liked you, Ezekiel.
你的人会在救世堂的栅栏上
Your people are gonna look up at the Sanctuary fence,
看到他们死去的国王
and they're gonna see their king...is dead.
继续装车
Keep loading the trucks.
国王大人敢做任何事  打断他的手
His Highness tries anything, break his arms.
不再闹着玩了
Tired of playin' bean bag.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
真的
I am.
米琼恩
Michonne.
Michonne!
卡尔
Carl.
朱迪思
Judith.
米琼恩
Michonne.
这游戏不再好玩了
This shit isn't funny anymore.
别逼我现在杀你  瑞克
Don't make me do this now, Rick.
我还给你安排了计划
I got plans for you.
把你一块块剁碎
Cut you up in little bitty pieces,
喂给行尸  同时逼你看着
feed you to the dead, and make you watch.
然后  当你变成了
Then, when you're some sort of
只有头的扭曲人彘后
screwed-up, creepy stump with a head...
我再杀了你
...that's when I'm gonna kill you --
当着所有人的面
in front of everybody.
-你他妈从来不闭嘴吗  -不闭
- You ever shut the hell up? - ‭Nope!
你知道你儿子自愿赴死吗
You know your kid volunteered to die?
你是怎么教儿子的  瑞克
What kind of boy you raise, Rick?
我会修好他的
I'm gonna fix him.
因为我喜欢他
'Cause I like him.
过几年
A few years,
他就会成为我的得力手下
he's gonna be one of my top guys!
等我处理完你以后
When I am done with you,
永远不会有人再做你做的事
nobody will ever try to do what you did --
永远不会
not ever again!
你的朋友不会  你的儿子不会
Not your friends, not your son --
不准碰她
Don't you touch her!
该死
Shit.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
你错过了  你们都错过了
And you missed it -- all of you.
都是你的错
This is your fault.
米琼恩
Michonne!
他们在哪
Where are they?
天啊
Oh...God.
我带他来的
I brought him here.
就是这样
That's how it happened.